

**DOWNLOAD CV** 

# Myroslav Zastavnyi

I am a person with quite a lot of work and life experience. I am an enthusiastic, goal-oriented, reliable, responsible, and hard-working person. I am a mature team worker and able to adapt to any difficult situation. I can work well both in a team and on my own initiative. I can work well under pressure and adhere to deadlines. I am a pleasant, cheerful, and friendly person. I have an analytical mindset and am always ready for new challenges. I am well organized and always plan ahead to manage my time properly. I have two higher educations - medical and lawyer. He was recognized as the best medical representative of 2016 (implemented the sales plan from 2015-2021). Since 2014, I have been engaged in charitable activities at the "Orpheus-IF" Charitable Foundation. The start of the war in Ukraine gave me some free time (since I am currently unemployed). Revise my life prospects and study what I have wanted for a long time: IT technologies.

#### CONTACTS

- +3 8068 5418628
- @Myroslav Zastavnyi
- Omerta85
- Omerta85
- Myroslav Zastavnyi
- 666Omerta@gmail.com
- Ivano-Frankivsk, UKRAINE

#### TECHNICAL SKILLS

- HTML5 / CSS3 / SASS(SCSS)
- JavaScript
- MYSQL, MONGODB
- GIT / GitHub
- TypeScript, React.JS, Angular, Node
- QA manual
- Nest.js(in progress)
- Scrum

#### **EDUCATION**

#### SIGMA SOFRWARE UNIVERSITY

SOFTWARE TESTING (IT Generation) (OCT 2022 - FEB 2023)

#### OKTEN PROGRAMMING SCHOOL

Course «JAVASCRIPT COMPLEX» (JUN 2022 - in progress)

#### **Vasyl Stefanyk Precarpathian National University**

Law Degree Lawyer

2010-2013

#### Ivano-Frankivsk National Medical University

Doctor medecine forensic medical expert 2002-2013

# LANGUAGES

ENGLISH beginner

POLISH beginner UKRAINIAN native

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### Biopharma

Key Account Manager of Pharmaceutical company

November 2015 - October 2021

- Promotion of drugs in the hospital segment + retail.
- Use of the tender channel of product promotion. Implementation of all necessary types of promotional activity (medical staff,
- hospital administrators, patient associations, etc.).
- Organization of training events for medical workers.
- Maintaining contractual and corporate reporting documentation. My achievements:
- The best medical representative of Ukraine for sales of anti-rhesus immunoglobulin in 2016.
- Execution of the sales plan by 100% or more in 2017, 2018, 2019. and 2020

#### **Eye Microsurgery Clinic "AS" (Medicine and Health)**

Senior Manager

March 2015 - November 2015

- Driving and influencing the culture and people aspects of organizational change to improve business efficiency and growth.
- Assisting the customization of HR procedures and policies, and ensuring they are followed by employees.
- Implementation of all necessary types of promotional activity (medical staff,
- hospital administrators, patient associations, etc.).
- Supporting the research, design and development of HR initiatives. Providing timely & efficient solutions to any issues from managers and team
- members.
- Maintaining contractual and corporate reporting documentation. Negotiating the conclusion of a contract for the operation. Execution of sales plans.

#### Pharmaceutical company Ananta, Yuria-Farm, Megalifesainth

Medical Representative

January 2012 - March 2015

- Maintained and made contacts with representatives of the health care sector.
- Represented the interests of the Company in a professional environment.
- Conducted educational events (seminars, round tables, presentations).
- Helped in the organization and participated in conferences.
- Carried out marketing activities.
- Reported on work performed. Adhere to the principles of ethical business conduct of the Company.

# **PROJECTS**

# **Project films**



Project structure: actions(getMovies, getGenres), redux store(made a list of movies, genres), components(header,moviesList, stars rating, userinfo, etc), containers(moviesPage). The main task: created a page with a list of movies, created a sweatshirt with a dark theme, created asynchronous requests. In addition, pagination was also created, as well as the following page with an extended

description of the film

technology stack: HTML, CSS, JavaScript,React

# **RICK AND MORTY**



The main task: created a page with a list and sidebar, created asynchronous

requests.

technology stack:

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Angular

# **Website of Charitable Foundation "A-HELP"**

The main task: is the development of the website of CF A-HELP according to the requirements of the customer (CF) and taking into account the technical capabilities of Sigma Software.



technology stack:

✓ HTML, CSS, React, Python

# Main responsibilities:

Requirements analysis and clarifications; Creation and update of test documentation (test plan, checklists, test cases, bug reports, etc.); Functional testing, regression testing, etc. Reports creation;

# Online Zoo



Online-zoo is a platform that collects information about animals from various zoos with webcams. It is assumed that the user can open a zoo resource page, watch one of the animals, or make a donation that will be used to purchase food. technology stack:

HTML, JavaScript, SASS, CSS.



CV (DOWNLOAD CV) My CV page

technology stack: HTML, CSS, JavaScript



# **SOFT SKILLS**

- Time management
- Teamwork and communication skills
- Ability to work in multitask mode and strict deadlines
- Creative thinking, proactivity
- Customer focus
- Purposefulness and the ability to bring what has been started to the end



CERTIFICATES

SOFTWARE TESTING

IT-support Google

IBM Full Stack Software

**COURSE** 

Developer

